Way to ruin the weekend. Tommy.
- The weekend just started. babe.
- And you already ruined it.
Forever's a long time.
No.
No. it-it'll be over
before we know it.
so we better not waste a second.
I need to drill
an existing well.
And what's the loan amount?
I'd say $325 to $350 million.
Don't you worry about a thing.
The answer is yes.
What are the odds
that we reach the gas field?
Ten percent.
I need more than a belief.
This is risking it all.
Chips to the middle.
But if it misses.
we're out $400 million dollars.
We all need
to explain this to Cami.
What's your hurry. son?
All those problems
you're racing home to fix
is problems when you get there.
I am the road map
to living life wrong.
You got it all. son.
but you're too stupid to see it.
I'm off the clock.
and from now on. starting today.
I'm gonna enjoy my life.
It's gonna be a hot one.
- 107.
- Yeah. in the shade.
In the shade.
So pull out them straw hats.
- And stay hydrated.
- Might I recommend
a cold. refreshing Modelo?
- With a lime.
- And some salt.
- That's a margarita.
- No. you got to try it.
- I'm telling you.
- Let's play something
appropriate to the temperature.
How about a little
"Cotton Fire"?
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Getting an early start. Nate?
I'm just doing a risk analysis
to see what's more expensive...
drilling the well
or getting sued.
What'd you come up with?
We're pretty fucked either way.
Well. that's the spirit. Nate.
Thinking like a winner.
I don't think
winning is an option here.
What we need
is the least damaging defeat.
I don't think that was
Washington's battle cry
at Bunker Hill. Nate.
Interesting fact.
Washington wasn't
present at Bunker Hill.
William Prescott
led the colonial army.
And the battle
actually took place
on Breed's Hill
and was a tactical defeat
for the colonials.
- In fact. I might add...
- Nate. Nate.
Have you been
in Dale's Adderall?
You think I give a shit
at seven o'clock in the morning
who won the fucking
Battle of Bunker Hill?
Look. we're standing here.
this is America.
Obviously we won something.
Son.
Pop?
Am I talking
to your fucking ghost?
- Where are you?
- Over here.
What are you doing?
I fell.
Made it back this far.
but now I'm stuck.
Just get up and walk out. shit.
Oh. gee.
why didn't I think of that?
With my knees and my hip.
I can't fucking stand right now.
All right.
There's a guy back at the home.
Alzheimer's.
Bad case of it.
Don't even know
how to put on his socks.
Fucker just stares
at the wall all day.
drooling all over himself.
Every few minutes. just...
he laughs.
No telling
what he's th-thinking.
But he sure looks happy.
It's a curse. my mind is sharp.
I get to sit here
and process all the ways...
my body is failing me.
Dying before
my failing fucking eyes.
Well. Pop. what happened to
"I'm gonna enjoy
whatever time I got left"?
It fell in
the fucking pool. son.
Pop. we just got
to get you moving.
You know?
Get you a physical therapist
or something like that.
You don't understand.
This skin suit is wore out.
You ain't wore out. Pop.
You're just stove-up.
Come on. let's go.
I got this far.
I just can't turn around
on these fucking steps.
Well. here.
just face towards me.
Give me your arm.
There you go.
I'll get you some dry clothes.
It's 98 fucking degrees
out here.
They'll be dry soon enough.
Well. I'm gonna
change my clothes.
Just stay away from
the edge. all right?
He okay?
He's the farthest thing
from okay. Nate.
Yes. sir.
You on your way?
I'll be there
in like 20 minutes.
I'll be there in 15.
Drive faster.
Hey. baby.
You left without saying goodbye.
I'm sorry. honey.
I had to get an early start.
Y'all laying out today?
Lord. no.
It's way too hot out.
Why you wearing a bikini?
'Cause I'm about
to ask you for some money.
Good God. How much?
Can I take $10.000
from the safe?
What the hell
do you need $10.000 for?
Well. 'cause I want to take
my old folks to the casino.
and we need
some money for gambling.
Where is there a casino?
- Carlsbad.
- Why don't you
give 'em a bunch of nickels
and park 'em
in front of a slot machine?
Nickels don't
change lives. baby.
They're
90 fucking years old. babe.
I think their lives
are done changing.
Oh. baby.
I'm in a life-changing mood.
And I'm feeling lucky.
How about you. Tommy?
Are you feeling lucky?
I'm gonna
rationalize it like this.
If I was in Amsterdam
and you were one of them hookers
in the little glass case
and it cost $10.000 to fuck you.
would I pay? Yes.
Baby. that is just so sweet.
Ten thousand dollars buys
Saturday night sex.
so you better lock
them fucking extensions down.
I love you.
and you are one
sexy motherfucker.
Mwah!
Ten thousand dollars.
Goddamn.
Always wondered if y'all
cleaned those things.
Can I help you?
Tell you what.
if I knew it paid this well.
I'd have been climbing up
them poles myself maybe.
Not sure you'd make much tips.
but you might get arrested.
I assume you work here.
Nah. I just wandered in
off the street
to count a stack of 20s
'cause I like the atmosphere.
You're a pistol. ain't you?
Well...
I got a job proposition for you.
And that's when
I scream for the bouncer.
No. it's not like that.
it's not even for me.
It's for my dad.
He's 82 years old.
and he's ate-up with arthritis
and all kind of injuries.
and he can barely get from one
end of the couch to the other.
Now. I figure.
your line of work.
you probably got
to stay pretty limber. right?
- It helps.
- So. you do
stretches and the yoga
and all that kind of thing?
Three hours a day
in the gym. buddy.
So. essentially. you're
your own physical therapist.
If you're really stretching
the definition. sure.
Could you help my dad?
Just show him
some of your stretches
to get him stronger.
Be no sex.
don't have to wear high heels
and a G-string or any of that.
Like a physical therapist?
Exactly.
Why don't you hire
a physical therapist?
Well. because my pop is
as stubborn as a jack mule.
But he can't say no
to a pretty woman.
All right. look.
It's an hour a day. twice a week
to help an old man.
Here.
That's him right there.
He looks sad.
He is sad.
I've seen
these two in here before
with a bunch of old folks.
I'll bet you.
This one here.
she likes to volunteer.
She's my wife.
My ex-wife.
We're back together now. though.
so she's kind of like
a ex-wife/fiancée.
Why don't they work him out?
It'd be a little weird.
don't you think?
'Cause this ain't weird?
Well. it's a little odd.
but it's innocent.
And you can do it
with your clothes on.
I like taking off my clothes.
Well. you can do it naked.
I don't give a shit.
He seems sweet.
Why not? But just so you know.
there's a sergeant
on Odessa SWAT
that keeps my location
in his phone.
Duly noted.
Now. if you want to give him
the occasional hand job
or something like that...
I was just tossing it out there.
It's not a requirement.
I mean.
j-just forget anything I said...
- Give me an address.
- Oh. yeah.
- What's your phone number?
- Yeah. All right. Hang on.
That's me right there.
You just put it in your deal?
- What time?
- Time don't matter.
He just sits out there
and watches the sun set.
Well. I'll head over there
this afternoon. then.
I appreciate it.
What's his name?
Thomas.
Everybody calls him T.L.
And just so you know.
I'm in no way
qualified to do this.
so if he breaks his back
or something.
I'm not taking any shit for it.
I assume all responsibility.
Cooper.
Sorry. y'all.
I had to make a little detour.
All good.
We ain't got nowhere else to be.
Well. you do now.
Boy wonder here
bought some leases
and started drilling.
working some wells over.
and hitting.
We're gonna take 'em over.
Let's get eyes on 'em.
- All right?
- All right.
- Yep.
- One more thing.
Project manager.
Anybody got a problem with that?
I don't mean
no disrespect. Tommy.
but he was just worming
for me a few months ago.
He knows what he don't know.
and he ain't too proud
to ask for advice.
He went six for six. Boss.
So. if it's
dumb luck. let's keep him dumb
as long as we can.
- All right?
- You got it.
- Lead the way.
- Let's go.
Let's go make some
fucking money. boys.
- Whoo!
- Did he say six for six?
- Six for six.
- Oh. shit.
Hello.
You gonna meet me at the FBO?
I'm gonna join by Zoom.
I'm still compiling data.
Rebecca and Charles
are at the FBO.
I'll call you
when we get set up.
I'll be here.
Are you sure
this thing won't fall over?
Strapped it to the chair. baby.
Gas pedal's the one
on the right. Margaret.
I don't want them
to spill their drinks.
I don't want 'em
drinking at all.
but I'd rather they
drink 'em than wear 'em.
Oh. my.
This drink's strong...
My son would say you're based.
- What's that mean?
- It's kind of like cool.
but you go
against the mainstream.
Do it your way.
Don't give a damn
what other people think.
Should we turn the music down?
They're starting to nap.
Couldn't have timed it
better. baby.
They'll be ready for round two
when we get there.
I was saying your mama's based.
Mm. So based.
And so hot.
Sure.
but if you could just be one.
would you be based or hot?
- Hot.
Are you crazy?
Well. I ain't either. so...
What?
You are both.
Please.
Who's driving this van?
Who bought the tequila?
Who ratcheted that fucking
margarita machine to the chair?
Yep. Pretty based to me.
Okay. weird.
You know what I'm thinking?
Mm-hmm. Makeover.
Oh. Lord.
I want one of these.
- It's a little painful.
- Relax.
It's worth it.
Trust me. Look up.
Give me some room. baby.
I got one more thing to do here.
Oh.
Oh. I don't think so.
I think yes.
No. I think not for me.
I think not your decision.
Do you know why
God made a woman's hips
wider than a man?
To open the parturition passage
- for ease of childbirth.
- So men will stare at them.
How's a man supposed
to look at your hips
if you've got your pants
pulled up like Mr. Magoo?
That's not
medically accurate. but...
Wide hips.
narrow waist.
large breasts.
nice plump round ass.
- That's right.
- Mammaries
provide sustenance to offspring.
and in the case of mammals.
those offspring are completely
dependent upon that sustenance
while their disproportionately
large brains form.
The female pelvis
is flared for the birthing.
hence wide hips.
Yeah. yeah. all that's fine.
But ain't nobody birthing
and feeding nothing
till somebody
gets fucked. right?
You got a point.
Margaret. are you married?
Uh. yes.
Well. now your husband's
gonna be so fucking happy.
I don't know
what kind of car you drive.
but my guess is. you'll be
driving a new one within a week.
I like my car.
All right. we got to get
this party started.
Here they come.
- Hi.
- Hi!
- Oh. look.
- Whoa.
Oh. my God!
Get in.
- No luggage?
- No luggage.
It's pretty windy.
Gonna be bumpy.
I'm gonna ask you all to stay
seated with seat belts on.
You don't like to fly?
She. uh. she-she gets
a little worked up about it.
Safer than driving. honey.
Under certain circumstances.
I wouldn't want
to fly the fucking thing
into a tornado. but I wouldn't
want to drive into one either.
It's not... I-I'm fine.
Okay?
I have control issues.
and it's not...
Look. I've been in plenty
of car crashes.
You can walk away from those.
Plane's not going to crash.
Rebecca.
You can say that.
but you don't know it.
Oh. I know it.
You want to know why I know it?
Because I ain't
that fucking lucky.
- Free game. baby.
- Ah... Ah! Free game.
Free game?
I got a free game. too.
Leave 'em.
People are looking.
That's the point.
I don't think they're looking
because they like it.
When you go to a museum.
how much time do you spend
looking at ugly paintings?
It's very difficult
to argue with you.
I don't make it easy. Margaret.
How we doing. ladies?
- How we doing?
- You just keep feeding
this thing until it throws up.
Yeah! Well. that's the spirit.
Mama.
- Look at your little thing.
- We have a problem.
- What's that. baby?
- Hank and Bob
already lost
all the money we gave 'em.
We just got here.
Lost it all the same.
- All right. where are they?
- The roulette wheel.
All right. show me.
We'll be right back. ladies.
Okay?
- All right. all right.
- Okay. gotcha.
Bye.
Oh. Lord.
See that. Margaret?
You just got ogled.
Not a goal of mine.
You have any more money?
Yeah. I got...
What in the world
are you boys doing?
This is a sucker's game.
It's got the best odds.
The house has
a 35-to-one advantage.
If you're gonna bet roulette.
you just bet color.
I've seen far more people
lose betting colors
than picking numbers. ma'am.
Mm. Because
they don't have the stack
or stones to stick it through.
If you stick it through.
guaranteed to win.
There's no guarantees.
Want to bet?
You're welcome
to prove me wrong.
Oh. no.
You shouldn't have said that.
Oh. Lord. Here it comes.
- Hundred on black.
Come on. black.
No more bets.
You got it. You got it.
Red.
- Two hundred on black.
Down and dirty. down and dirty.
Red.
- Come on.
Red?
Aw. man.
Sixteen hundred on black.
Come on now. black.
Come on. come on.
Come on. jump. jump.
Mama.
Relax. baby.
- Oh. my God.
- Time for a black now. isn't it?
- Come on. go for it. go for it.
- No more bets.
- Ah!
- Man...
Sixty-four hundred on black.
I can't even look.
Let's go. do it. do it.
Black.
Black ten is
- the winner.
- Yes.
Let it ride.
- Okay.
- Let it ride.
Do it now. Do it now.
Do it now. You can do it.
- Whoo!
- Black.
Thirty-five black.
Let's go. Let it ride.
- Are you sure. ma'am?
- Let it ride.
Let it ride.
- Come on. black.
- Come on.
Come on.
black. black. black. black.
Black 31.
Oh. my goodness.
It's a good win.
You ready to cash out. ma'am?
Let it ride.
Ah! God.
All right. all right.
I believe. I believe!
You're gonna get it. Yeah.
Come on. black.
Let's go.
let's go. let's go. boy.
Black 24.
Whoo! Come on.
This just
brought tears to my eyes.
Oh. my God.
All right.
Got it?
- Got it.
- Yeah. we got it.
Start small.
- Yes. ma'am.
- Start small.
- That's beautiful.
- Thank you.
Hey. hey. hey.
Here.
Get a load of this
back at the home.
See y'all later.
Okay.
Wait. Am I wrong.
or did your mom
just win. like. $90.000?
She's like a superhero.
if superheroes wore Tom Ford.
You don't see that much anymore.
Reading an actual paper.
not a news app on a phone.
Well. you know.
it hurts my eyes
to stare at the phone.
Me. too.
You mind if I sit?
Oh. I-I don't mind.
Thank you.
Where you in from?
Oh. I live here.
My office is just next door.
I'm just waiting for a meeting.
What do you do for work?
Uh. well...
it's complicated.
Complicated is fun.
You have a little bit
of salad dressing.
You don't know me to touch me.
Did you not see this?
This means "not available."
Understood. My-my apologies.
Hey.
- How dare you?
- Hey. listen. I'm sorry.
Are you ready?
Thanks. Monica.
Thanks for seeing us. Cami.
Sorry about springing
this meeting
on you. but we wanted
our offshore geologist
to kind of walk you through
the possible outcomes here.
Well. I was unaware
that there was any other
outcome but one. Tommy.
Well. that's why we're here.
I'm gonna patch Nate through.
if it's all right.
This is Charles Newsom.
He's a geologist who specializes
in offshore drilling.
And who do you work for?
I work for you. ma'am.
I thought we didn't know
about this offshore rig.
I work the Permian
for you. ma'am.
Well. there's not
a lot of ocean out there.
No. ma'am. there's not.
I worked deepwater rigs for BP
and. uh. managed
intelligent drilling
as well as sand control
solutions for Halliburton
in the Gulf. near your
proposed drilling site.
So you know the area.
I know it well. ma'am. yes.
- We've got Nate.
- Okay...
Hello. Cami.
Hey there. Nate.
Yeah. go ahead. Sure.
Okay.
Right. So... there.
Your rig. uh.
was located right here.
And after eight years
of consistent production.
the rig attempted
to increase output
by running deeper by 5.000 feet
below the 29.000-feet depth
of the wellhead.
Now. as it pushed deeper.
the well started producing
sand and water at pressures
greater than the wellhead
could sustain.
and the rig manager
was forced to seal the wellhead
and shut the rig down.
Now. the question here is...
did you push through
an isolated pocket of gas.
or was this pocket indicative
of a much larger reservoir?
Which was your
original geologist's theory.
one that I tend
to agree with. given
the number of producing rigs
in the region. notated on here.
But currently these are mapped
as independent pockets of gas
and not a larger field.
I'm not sure I understand
what you're saying.
He's saying
there's no guarantee.
No guarantee?
That the drill
will be successful.
You could spend
$400 million dollars.
have absolute nothing
to show for it.
Is that what you're saying?
Well. there's never a guarantee.
But if there is a larger pocket
and you can increase your output
at the estimated tenfold.
then you're measuring
the output in the trillions.
not the millions.
Can someone help me
understand that?
Well. a rig that generates
$150 million in profits
generates billions over
the same time period.
Well. that sounds
like good news.
Why the serious faces?
Cami. you must understand.
the likelihood
of a successful strike
at the initial site is 10%.
A 10% chance of rain is
no chance at all. as you know.
We could be chasing this field
for the next decade
and never find it.
We believe
the reason Monty didn't drill
was that he felt a litigation
against the insurance company
was a safer strategy.
hence investing the money
and seeking returns.
uh. between 12 and 17%
year over year
to essentially
pay the settlement.
Well. how much
is the settlement?
That's undetermined.
We would. of course.
extend litigation
for as long as possible.
say. three or four years.
and litigation costs would be
in the ten-to-15 million-dollar
range per annum.
$400 million at 15%.
that's $60 million a year.
Times four. that's 240.
Now. if we settle with ROI.
we keep every dime
of their money.
And what about the principle?
Principal's never touched.
I'm not talking about the money.
I'm talking about the
insurance company's position
that we misappropriated
the payout.
Cami. it's
a multinational corporation.
Uh. they don't have principles.
They have balance sheets
and quarterly earnings reports
and stuff like that.
If it goes to trial.
we could Chapter 11
and they get nothing.
and they know that.
So you think we should litigate?
Yes. I do.
And you think you can win.
It's not a win-or-lose
situation for them.
It's "how do we recoup
as much of our $400 million
contractually obligated payout
on a technicality?"
A settlement's the only way.
But the rig is already
in motion. It's been leased.
We will cancel the lease.
Well. if we can just cancel it.
then what's the point
of having one?
If we never keep our word.
what's our word worth?
Nothing. Nobody's is.
That's what the lawyers are for.
And you think it's there?
There's no question it's there.
The question is. can we find it?
Can you?
Let me just show you something.
Here.
Now. you see this?
Could this be water?
Maybe.
But that would require
water to defy gravity.
Gas defies it already.
You think that's gas.
I think that's gas.
My word will be worth something.
Go find it.
Hey. thanks a lot.
You asked me to explain it.
so I explained it.
I said explain it.
not sell it
like a fucking time-share.
Hey. You know. me personally.
I prefer
the relationship to evolve
just a little bit further
before I start fucking lying
- for somebody.
- We don't have a relationship.
We had sex. and we
won't be doing that anymore.
- I can fucking promise you.
- Yeah. I see what it's like
with you. I do what you say
your way or you just
sever the relationship.
What a lonely woman
you're gonna be.
Anything else?
Cami.
You disagree.
Cami. we have
a performance clause on
the Wolf Camp Fields. too.
We can't service both.
You're abandoning
a sure thing for a maybe.
But. like you said.
it's your company.
Who knows. maybe you're right.
Tommy.
You know. my friends
won't call me back.
I guess they don't want
a rich widow
around their husbands.
I don't know.
Well. they weren't your friends
to begin with then.
I was at lunch today...
and a man. very handsome...
he touched my face.
He touched it like...
I just don't have anybody else
that I can talk to about it.
Hey.
Why don't you let me
sell this thing for you.
Get yourself
a big house on the beach.
Hire some cabana boys
to rub coconut oil on you.
I don't want cabana boys.
I want success.
Get that for me.
I'm trying.
Hey. Monica.
Where'd everybody go?
Downstairs.
Okay. Thank you. honey.
See y'all at the FBO.
I got another meeting.
All right.
Hey.
You okay?
Fine.
Meet you at the FBO.
All right.
I don't know what's in the water
these fucking women
are drinking.
I'm scared to go home tonight.
I'm just gonna tell him
he's got a ten percent chance
of ever seeing his money again.
Maybe the son of a bitch
will back off.
Tommy. she was pretty clear
it's what she wants.
She can want
all she wants to. Nate.
but it'll kill the company.
I got to do
what's best for the company.
which is what's best for her.
I don't disagree. but...
Hang on.
Can I help you?
You're not T.L.
I am not.
He has more hair.
Correct.
Is he here?
Can I ask
what this is referring?
I'm his physical therapist.
Right.
Nate?
Yes?
Listen. go with me
on this physical therapist.
Don't ask
too many questions. okay?
Down the hall. past the kitchen.
on the left.
Oh. y'all got a pool here.
Y-Yes. correct.
but it's not for public use.
j-just ours.
I'll-I'll explain it to you
later when I can talk. okay?
I don't want to know.
No. Hey...
You're not T.L.
I can be. I could be.
Wait!
T.L.?
Who are you?
I'm your physical therapist.
On what fucking planet
are you my physical therapist?
On this one. right now. today.
Hey. I saw you got a pool.
Ever done aquatherapy?
What's that?
Just watched a video on it.
You lay back.
I'll cradle you in my arms.
sway you back and forth.
You just kind of float.
Releases the pressure
in your joints. your back.
What do you say?
Just to be clear.
you're asking if I'd like
to be held in the water by you
while you sway back and forth?
That's what I'm asking.
I ain't got a bathing suit.
Undies is fine.
That's what I'll be wearing.
I. uh. I... My back.
The disc.
Uh. slipped.
- Ma'am?
- Oh. no.
I didn't get your name.
Get your own therapist. pal.
All right. This'll only
take me about ten minutes.
Right this way. Mr. Norris.
Yep.
Mr. Norris.
Send him in.
Tommy.
What a surprise.
It's not
that much of a surprise.
Everybody seemed
to be pretty ready for me
when I show up.
Security notified us when
your driver dropped you off.
Oh.
Oh. you don't
have security cameras
in your places of business?
We got 'em all over the place.
- Well. I would think so.
- Yeah.
How can I help you?
This offshore rig
has a ten percent success rate.
I thought there was a certainty
that gas exists there.
It is.
It's a ten percent chance
we find it.
Those are not good odds.
Pretty shitty.
You canceling the drill?
Nothing would please me more.
but Cami
wants to see it through.
Well. that sounds like
an emotional decision.
It is.
and I'm hoping you'll make
a practical one
and cease funding.
We signed a deal.
I know. but I'm giving you
permission to cancel it.
I didn't sign the deal
with you. Tommy.
You're gonna lose every penny
of your investment
in this venture.
Well. unless it works.
Ninety percent chance it won't.
- But if it does...
- It won't.
But if it does...
Why are we playing
this fucking game?
I'm telling you it won't work.
I know you guys are rich.
and you think
losing money and product
is just part of business.
but $400 million dollars?
Are you shitting me?
Is your boss so rich
he just don't give a fuck?
I gave her my word. Tommy.
Oh. for fuck's sake.
I just didn't
loan her the money.
I invested in her company.
The royalty payments
off the leases alone
will generate over
$300 million dollars a year.
I can shut down
this entire business
and pay myself back
in three years.
She secured
the loan with royalties?
Yes. of course.
Well. if the well's dry.
it's gonna clean her out.
Well. I wouldn't say
it cleans her out.
She has $280 million dollars
in assets in a trust.
Does it kill the company?
Absolutely.
but you and I know that
that company died
when her husband died.
The way he played
only works while he's playing.
But the music has stopped.
and he didn't
leave a chair for her.
And to be honest.
the best thing is.
the well is dry.
it's over quick.
She sells the pieces.
but she retires
a very. very wealthy woman.
Not as wealthy as you.
No. but that's what
$400 million dollars buys you.
And if you were in my position.
would you do different?
Nothing.
I'd do it the same.
You got to admire her. though.
She has no plan.
She just wants
to will gas out of that well.
It's called "wildcatting."
Drilling on a hunch.
Dreaming it out of the ground.
Her husband was the best.
but she ain't her husband.
Well. I guess we'll find out.
I have never heard
anybody make ten percent
sound like a better deal
than your ass just did.
Thank you.
I just told her the truth.
Uh-huh.
I'm mad too. honey. but goddamn.
Did you ever think
about doing yoga
or meditating or some shit?
You know. get your
heart rate down a little bit?
I know what he did
to make me mad.
but what the hell
did he do to make you so mad?
I had it coming.
Well. if you had it coming.
then why are you
sitting here
in the corner sulking?
I'm not sulking.
That's the definition of it.
If I looked it up
in the dictionary.
there'd be a picture
of you sitting back
in the corner of a jet airplane
with your ass cheeks
squeezed so tight.
you could crack fucking walnuts.
I'm sulking because
what he said is true.
And it hurt.
Truth has a funny way
of doing that. don't it?
Hey. you said you'd be late.
so I picked up some barbecue
from Brantley Creek.
I have had some strange days.
I will tell you.
But this one... whew.
Hey. turn around.
What in the...
The volunteers
did a makeover day. thing.
experiment out of me.
Have 'em do it again tomorrow.
Really?
Tomorrow.
You like it?
Do I like it?
I love it.
Hi. Daddy.
Hey. baby.
How was your day?
Magnificent. How was your day?
Kick in the balls.
Aw. I'm sorry.
What's with all the ball caps?
Tonight's dinner theme
is baseball.
Are we having peanuts?
Hot dogs. I didn't have time
to get to the store. baby.
I'm sorry.
This might be a dinner
I can get through.
actually get through.
Where's Pop?
The pool.
Again? And y'all just
left his ass out there?
Well. he definitely
ain't drowning.
They've been in there for hours.
Can you ask T.L. if his
hooker's staying for supper?
She ain't a hooker. honey.
She's a physical therapist.
Honey. her license plate
says "HOT LIPPS."
Well. she's also
a-a physical therapist.
I don't care. I'm happy for him.
I just want to know
how many hot dogs to make.
What is this?
Return on your investment.
Don't you businessmen like that?
We like it very much.
How much did you win?
Hundred on the roulette wheel.
but the craps table.
that's where it really
started going my way.
Hey. baby.
Did you happen to count how much
money your mama made here?
$317.622.
And 68 cents.
How the hell
do you win 68 cents?
Nickel slots. It was me.
Good job. baby.
So. you got any plans
for this money?
I mean. the question is.
do you have any plans
for this money? Hmm?
Oh. I can think of some plans.
Well. I'm all ears.
When I look at you.
I don't see ears. baby.
I didn't even know you had any.
It's gonna be a minute
before we get our hot dogs.
Sounds like someone's
getting a hot dog right now.
Dale!
Inappropriate.
Wrong thing to say
in front of a child.
It's okay.
Back feel better?
Everything feels better.
Knees. hips.
Everything.
Good.
Got a boyfriend. Cheyenne?
No.
My. uh. other job has instilled
a number of trust issues in me
when it comes to men.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Comes with the territory.
Maybe you need new territory.
Whatever I need.
I'll get it for myself.
How long do these
therapy sessions last?
I haven't given it much thought.
Are you bored?
Far from it.
You?
T.L.. I can do this all day.
You have been. darling.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-